If you remember anything at all about this lesson remember this.
如果你还记得这节课的任何内容，请记住这一点。
This is probably the most important thing to know when it comes to describing things clearly.
当要清楚地描述事物时，这可能是最重要的事情。
If you can do this well you should be able to describe anything you need to describe and put the idea
如果你能做到这一点，你应该能够描述任何你需要描述的东西并提出这个想法
of that thing very clearly in another person's mind.
那件事很清楚地在另一个人的脑海中。
So this is it.
所以就是这样。
OK.
好的。
We're going to look at these four very simple sentences and we're going to look at why it's bad.
我们将看看这四个非常简单的句子，我们将看看它为什么不好。
And then we're going to talk about how we can make it really clear the first sentence of a description
然后我们将讨论如何使描述的第一句话真正清晰
is really really important.
真的很重要。
If you say the basic details of something much much later when you're describing it then people will
如果你在描述某件事的时候说的基本细节很晚，那么人们会
be lost from the beginning.
从一开始就迷失。
Right.
正确的。
So we need to know how to say the most important simple details first like the foundation of a house.
所以我们首先需要知道如何说出最重要的简单细节，比如房子的地基。
Then we can build on that by adding things to it.
然后我们可以通过添加东西来建立它。
For example if we're telling a story if you just say and I was so scared because the horse jumped right
例如，如果我们正在讲一个故事，如果你只是说，我很害怕，因为马跳到了右边
over the fence and nearly crushed me.
越过栅栏，差点压死我。
People will say what horse What fence what's happening here.
人们会说什么马什么篱笆这里发生了什么。
But if we set the scene we say set the scene where when what Who what's going on here then people have
但是，如果我们设置场景，我们说设置场景，什么时候，谁，这里发生了什么，那么人们有
a clear picture of OK you're here.
一张清晰的照片，确定你在这里。
It was this time.
正是这个时候。
I know you know what how big the horse was and why you were in this place.
我知道你知道这匹马有多大，你为什么会在这个地方。
Then you can say how you felt then you can explain more details about what happened right then you can
然后你可以说出你的感受然后你可以解释更多关于发生的事情的细节然后你可以
talk about your ideas or whatever but you have to have that thing at the beginning.
谈论你的想法或其他任何东西，但你必须在一开始就有那个东西。
OK.
好的。
So let's look at these four sentences and talk about how we can do this how we can set the scene and
所以让我们看看这四个句子，谈谈我们如何做到这一点，我们如何设置场景和
give the basic details first in our description.
在我们的描述中首先给出基本细节。
So number one I have a car.
所以第一，我有车。
It's a Ford.
这是一辆福特。
Ford is a brand of car.
福特是汽车品牌。
I think you probably know that it has four doors.
我想你可能知道它有四个门。
It is yellow.
它是黄色的。
It has a good stereo the stereo is stereo.
它有一个很好的立体声音响是立体声的。
By the way if you don't know is the sound system in the car or when you have two speakers left and on
顺便说一句，如果您不知道是车内的音响系统，还是您有两个扬声器并打开时
the right.
正确的。
OK.
好的。
This is not good right.
这不好对。
Because so many sentences and each sentence only has really one piece of information.
因为这么多的句子，每个句子只有一个真正的信息。
One thing to know so it's not very good.
有一件事要知道，所以它不是很好。
It's better if we use one sentence maybe two to say all the basic details we need at the beginning of
我们最好用一句话或者两句话来把我们需要的所有基本细节在开头
a description.
说明。
I would recommend you use one sentence.
我建议你用一句话。
So rule number one use one sentence at the beginning of a description.
因此，第一条规则在描述的开头使用一个句子。
Use one very clear sentence.
使用一个非常清楚的句子。
Rule number two is use more than one adjective.
第二条规则是使用多个形容词。
More than one adjective.
不止一个形容词。
I'm going to write a D.J..
我要写一个D.J..
That's a J.
那是一个J。
More than one adjective when you're describing something in front of your main noun OK.
当您在主要名词 OK 前描述某事时，不止一个形容词。
So just to be clear adjectives things like yellow.
所以要明确形容词，比如黄色。
Right.
正确的。
And we can make other adjectives to make it clear what we're talking about.
我们可以使用其他形容词来明确我们在说什么。
We can use more than one but we also need to know what our main noun is.
我们可以使用多个，但我们还需要知道我们的主要名词是什么。
So we have to choose a main noun and then put three or four adjectives in front of that to make it really
所以我们必须选择一个主要名词，然后在它前面加上三四个形容词才能使它真正
really clear what we're talking about and to give the other person a very clear picture.
非常清楚我们在说什么，并给对方一个非常清晰的画面。
OK.
好的。
So more than one adjective and three have a main noun.
所以不止一个形容词和三个有一个主要名词。
So we use one sentence we use more than one adjective and we have a main noun.
所以e 使用一个句子我们使用多个形容词并且我们有一个主要名词。
Let's look at how we can do that with these sentences.
让我们看看如何用这些句子做到这一点。
OK.
好的。
So which of these can we turn into or use as adjectives for the main noun.
那么我们可以将其中哪些变成或用作主要名词的形容词。
And which is the main noun.
这是主要名词。
Well this sentence is not really necessary.
好吧，这句话不是真的必要。
So we can cancel it if Ford is R may noun because Ford is a kind of car right.
因此，如果 Ford 是 R 可能名词，我们可以取消它，因为 Ford 是一种汽车对。
So if we say Ford is our main noun we don't need that and maybe we can even add more information.
因此，如果我们说福特是我们的主要名词，我们就不需要它，也许我们甚至可以添加更多信息。
Let's say this this Ford is from let's say it's from 1998 right.
假设这辆福特是 1998 年的吧。
Let's say it's nineteen ninety eight.
假设现在是十九九十八。
That's an adjective.
那是一个形容词。
1998 can be used as an adjective can be yellow.
1998 可以用作形容词，可以是黄色的。
Obviously yellow is an adjective for doors.
显然黄色是门的形容词。
Can that be made into an adjective.
能不能做成形容词。
Yes.
是的。
If you have something like a five year old child write a five year old child or five year old girl for
如果你有一个五岁的孩子，写一个五岁的孩子或五岁的女孩
example or 32 page book all you're doing there is adding a hyphen it's a hyphen.
示例或 32 页的书，你所做的只是添加一个连字符，它是一个连字符。
It's called a hyphen.
它被称为连字符。
H y p h e n h y p yet.
H y p h e n h y p 还没有。
And you're making it into an adjective.
而你正在把它变成一个形容词。
A 42 hyphen page book a five hyphen year hyphen old girl five year old girl.
一本 42 页连字符的书 一个五岁连字符的老女孩 五岁的女孩。
You're making new adjectives so all we have to do to make this an adjective is take.
你正在制作新的形容词，所以我们要做的就是把它变成形容词。
S Because adjectives can not be plural can have yellows for example and we make it for hyphen door for
S 因为形容词不能是复数，例如可以有黄色，我们把它做成连字符门
door.
门。
So let's see what we can do.
所以让我们看看我们能做些什么。
May noun for adjective nineteen 1998 for door adjective yellow adjectives so we're gonna use three adjectives
五月名词形容词十九 1998 门形容词黄色形容词所以我们要用三个形容词
here in front of the main note we could do four but let's use three for now and then in the same sentence
在主音前面我们可以做四个，但让我们偶尔在同一个句子中使用三个
we're going to put with them we're going to add something about the stereo we can do the same thing
我们要和他们一起我们要添加一些关于立体声的东西我们可以做同样的事情
with in sometimes if we want to say the location but this is all going to be one sentence so let's try
有时如果我们想说位置，但这都是一句话，所以让我们试试
this I have a yellow four door 1998 Ford and if we wanted to say what type of car it is maybe an SUV
我有一辆黄色的四门 1998 福特，如果我们想说它是什么类型的汽车，它可能是 SUV
or a van or a truck if it's a special type of vehicle then that's your new main noun it's a yellow Ford
或面包车或卡车，如果它是一种特殊类型的车辆，那么这是你的新主要名词它是黄色福特
or 98 98 Ford SUV now SUV is the main noun and Ford becomes like an adjective it's used as an adjective.
或 98 98 Ford SUV 现在 SUV 是主要名词，而 Ford 变得像一个形容词，它被用作形容词。
But let's just say Ford for now I have a yellow Ford or a 1998 Ford with a good stereo look at this
但是让我们说福特现在我有一辆黄色的福特或 1998 年的福特，它的立体效果很好
one sentence and we have so much information a yellow very clear four door OK.
一句话我们有这么多资料一黄很清楚四门OK。
Got it.
知道了。
Nineteen ninety eight OK.
十九九十八行。
Kind of old Ford brand.
有点老福特品牌。
Got it with a good stereo I have a very clear picture now in my mind I didn't need to make many sentences
用好的立体声得到它我现在脑海里有一个非常清晰的画面我不需要说很多句子
a nice say it right at the beginning so now I can say something else about it now maybe I can tell a
一开始就说得很好，所以现在我可以说点别的了，也许我可以说
story about my 1998 car my 1998 Ford right I can tell a story because you started with this clear picture
关于我 1998 年汽车的故事 我 1998 年福特汽车的故事 我可以讲一个故事，因为你从这张清晰的图片开始
in your mind the story will now make sense.
在你的脑海里，这个故事现在变得有意义了。
So whatever we add after it it's going to make more sense because the first sentence was extremely clear.
所以无论我们在它后面添加什么，它都会更有意义，因为第一句话非常清楚。
OK.
好的。
This is the main idea.
这是主要思想。
This is the most important thing to learn about description if you can do this.
如果你能做到这一点，这是了解描述的最重要的事情。
Choose your main noun.
选择你的主要名词。
Have several adjectives.
有几个形容词。
Two three four sometimes five if you can turn some things into adjectives like four door and you can
二三四有时五如果你能把一些东西变成形容词，比如四门，你可以
use nouns as adjectives like 1998 and Ford if we want to say SUV if you can do that then you become
使用名词作为形容词，例如 1998 和 Ford，如果我们想说 SUV，如果你能做到，那么你就变成
a lot more powerful with your descriptions and then you can add more stuff after it in the same sentence
您的描述更强大，然后您可以在同一句子中添加更多内容
with a good stereo.
具有良好的立体声。
Now let's see if we can do this with a real picture.
现在让我们看看我们是否可以用真实的图片来做到这一点。
We're going to take a picture and we're going to talk about how we can describe it clearly as part of
我们要拍张照片，我们要讨论如何清楚地描述它作为
a kind of story or the beginning of a story.
一种故事或故事的开始。